totalchoicehosting.com 2016-06-29

# Privacy Policy | Totalchoice Hosting

##  Privacy  Policy

TotalChoice Hosting, Inc. is committed to protecting the privacy of our clients. By using our services, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy. We provide this notice to explain our information and data practices and keep it readily available via the “Privacy Policy” link in the footer of our homepage and various pages throughout.

**Privacy:**

We collect a very small amount of data necessary to provide you with the best service possible. Data may be collected via any of our products or services (chat system, help desk, forum, blog, hosting account, domains etc.) and is strictly used internally. Anything collected will never be sold to any third parties. This does not apply to affiliates that provide services to you based on links provided within your cPanel access and control, wherein information will be shared to facilitate your use of additional amenities included with the hosting services we provide. We oblige by all state and federal laws as well as the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles and your privacy is a top priority of ours. 

**Use of Data:**

Some of our services require the use of your billing information for support purposes. Because we take your privacy and protection very seriously, we may ask for various forms of identity verification during the support process. All bank and credit card information is processed only for billing purposes for any product or service you signed up for with TotalChoice Hosting. We strive to keep all information safe and use secure browsing when possible. Users of our products and services are subject to receiving e-mails from us, such as maintenance notices and our monthly newsletter but may opt-out at any time. 

We use IP addresses to analyze and administer our site and servers, track access and provide security to our server farm. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. It is possible that personal information about a customer may be included in the log files due to the normal functions of IP addresses and Web browsing.

**Opt Out:**

By default, users of all of our services are subscribed to our maintenance updates and newsletter. Members of our forum and users of the blog may also receive e-mails from TotalChoice Hosting or its authorized contractors. You may opt out at any time via the appropriate links provided in the e-mails.

**Cookies:**

Your web browser has a built in system that helps websites recognize your computer and online accounts via small text files called ‘Cookies’. Cookies are used to provide seamless, personalized functionality such as saving your login information and site preferences. Although you are able to disable cookies via your web browser preferences, we recommend keeping them enabled on our website.

**Updating Your Personal Information:**

If you are a subscriber to any of our services, you may update or change your personal information at any time. Please use the appropriate dashboard to adjust your information or create a support ticket at our help desk via [https://support.totalchoicehosting.com](https://support.totalchoicehosting.com/).

**Policy Amendments:**

We may amend this policy at any time and will always keep it posted on our website for reference. Any amendment supersedes all previous versions of the privacy policy. We recommend you check the policy regularly to stay current. 

**Contacting Us:**

You may contact us at any time via our ‘Contact Us’ page or alternatively via US MAIL:

TotalChoice Hosting, Inc.  
PO Box 518  
Oxford, MI 48371
